pressmediawire.com 2011-12-01

# 

Updated: May 17, 2011

**PressMediaWire.com** is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy describes how **** PressMediaWire.com collects and uses the personal information you provide on our website: PressMediaWire.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding PressMediaWire.com's use of your personal information and the steps you can take to access this information and to request that we correct or update it.

**We collect the following personal information from you:**

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number
  * Unique Identifiers such as user name and password.

As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system.

**We use this information to:**

  * Fulfill your order
  * Send you an order confirmation
  * Assess the needs of your business to determine suitable products
  * Send you requested product or service information
  * Send product updates or warranty information
  * Respond to customer service requests
  * Administer your account
  * Send you marketing communications
  * Administer contests and sweepstakes you entered, and notify you if you won
  * Respond to your questions and concerns
  * Improve our Web site and marketing efforts
  * Conduct research and analysis

**Information Obtained from Third Parties**

If you provide us personal information about others, or if others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us.

#### Information Sharing

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information **only** to perform the service they are providing for us.

We may also disclose your personal information

  * as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process,
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * if PressMediaWire.com. is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

**Payments**

Our payment mode is through PAYPAL. You will provide your credit card number, directly to PayPal. PayPal's privacy policy will apply to the information you provide on the PayPal Web site.

#### Tracking Technologies

We or a third party contracted by us may use technologies such as cookies, Web beacons, or scripts to gather information about how you and others interact with our Web site. For example, we will know how many users access a specific areas or features within our site and which links or ads they clicked on. We use this aggregated information to understand and optimize how our site is used, improve our marketing efforts, and provide content and features that are of interest to you.

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of PressMediaWire.com. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit.

#### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at helpdesk@pressmediawire.com

#### Additional Policy Information

**Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information**

To review and update your personal information to ensure it is accurate, contact us at helpdesk@pressmediawire.com

**Notification of Privacy Statement Changes**

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

Our Web site includes Widgets, which are interactive mini-programs that run on our site to provide specific services from another company (e.g. displaying the news, opinions, music, etc). Personal information, such as your email address, may be collected through the Widget. Cookies may also be set by the Widget to enable it to function properly. Information collected by this Widget is governed by the privacy policy of the company that created it.

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them.

#### Contact Information

You can contact us about this privacy statement by writing or email us at the address below:

PressMediaWire.com.

504 Florida Avenue

Herndon, VA 20170

Email: helpdesk@pressmediawire.com[](mailto:privacy@freshelement.com)
